Register of the Commission for Relief in Belgium Records, 1914-1930
Hoover Institution Archives
- LONDON OFFICE LACE DEPARTMENT FILE, 1915-1920
  - Financial records. Includes some correspondence
    - Statements
      - Salvage charges (Folder 8)
    - Trial balance (Folder 9-10)
- NEW YORK OFFICE ACCOUNTS, 1914-1922
  - Canceled checks (Box 137)
    - Guaranty Trust Company of New York (expenses include food supplies, freights, clothing, etc.)
      - 1914 November-December (#1-#219) (Folder 1)
      - 1915
        - January (#220-#545) (Folder 2)
        - February (#546-#735) (Folder 3)
        - March (#736-#920, #A1-#A97) (Box 138, Folder 1)
        - April (#A98-#A278) (Folder 2)
        - May (#A279-#A547) (Folder 3)
        - June (#A548-#A735) (Box 139, Folder 1)
        - July (#A736-#A862) (Folder 2)
        - August (#A866-#A993) (Folder 3)
        - September (#A996-#A1141) (Folder 4)
      - 1916 (Box 140)
        - March (#A2420-#A2672) (Folder 1)
        - April (#A2673-#A2917) (Folder 2)
        - May (#A2919-#A3197) (Folder 3)
        - June (#A3199-#A3566) (Box 141, Folder 1-2)
        - July (#A3567-A#3925) (Folder 3-4)
        - December (#A5088-#A5448) (Box 142, Folder 1-2)
      - 1917
        - January (#A5449-#A5855) (Folder 3-4)
        - February (#A5856-#A6158 (Box 143, Folder 1-2)
        - March (#A6159-#A6514) (Folder 3-4)
        - April (#A6515-#A6733) (Box 144, Folder 1)
        - May (#A6734-#A6965) (Folder 2)
        - June (#A6966-#A7175) (Folder 3)
        - July (#A7176-#A7403) (Box 145, Folder 1)
        - August (#A7404-#A7659) (Folder 2)
        - September (#A7660-#A7849) (Folder 3)
        - October (#A7850-#A8465) (Box 146, Folder 1-3)
        - November
          - (#A8466-#A8736) (Folder 4)
          - (#A8737-#A8970) (Box 147, Folder 1)
        - December (#A8971-#A9311) (Folder 2-3)
      - 1919 (Box 148)
        - January (#A14112-#A14285) (Folder 1)
        - February (#A14286-#A14433) (Folder 2)
        - March (#A14434-#A14649) (Folder 3-4)
        - April (#A14650-#A14852) (Box 149, Folder 1-2)
        - May (#A14853-#A15031 (Folder 3)
        - June (#A15032-#A15235) (Folder 4)
        - July (#A15236-#A15396) (Box 150, Folder 1)
        - August (#A15397-#A15585) (Folder 2)
        - September (#A15586-#A15746) (Folder 3)
        - October (#A15747-#A15900) (Box 151, Folder 1)
        - November (#A15901-#A16039) (Folder 2)
        - December (#A16040-16329) (Folder 3-4)
    - National City Bank of New York (payroll) (Box 152)
      - 1915
        - February (No. 1-121) (Folder 1)
        - August (#B1116-#B1218) (Folder 2)
        - September (#B1219-#B1318) (Folder 3)
        - October (#B1319-#B1429) (Folder 4)
        - November (#B1430-#B1566) (Folder 5)
        - December (#B1567-#B1717) (Folder 6)
      - 1916 (Box 153)
        - January (#B1718-#B1887) (Folder 1)
        - February (#B1888-#B2060) (Folder 2)
        - March (#B2061-#B2217) (Folder 3)
        - April (#B2218-#B2359) (Folder 4)
        - May (#B2360-#B2487) (Folder 5)
        - June (#B2489-#B2615) (Box 154, Folder 1)
        - July (#B2616-#B2746) (Folder 2)
        - August (#B2747-#B2880) (Folder 3)
        - September (#B2881-#B2991) (Folder 4)
        - October (#B2992-#B3092) (Folder 5)
        - November (#B3093-#B3198) (Folder 6)
        - December (#B3199-#B3307) (Box 155, Folder 1)
      - 1917
        - January (#B3308-#B3468) (Folder 2)
        - February (#B3469-#B3585) (Folder 3)
        - March (#B3586-#B3698) (Folder 4)
        - April (#B3699-#B3807) (Folder 5)
    - Miscellany financial institutions, 1914-1915 (Folder 6)
  - Claim records - Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Company, Chesapeake Export Company (claim no. 322). Correspondence, legal documents, lists of freights, goods, and damages (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Commercial exchange records
    - General
      - 1915-1916 (#1-#1295) (Folder 2)
      - 1917-1918 (#2663-#3774) (Folder 3)
      - 1918 (#3775-#4970) (Folder 4)
    - London Special Accounts Department, 1915-1919 (bound volumes) (Box 157, Folder 1-4)
  - Correspondence (Box 158)
    - New York - Brussels
      - General, 1919-1920 (Folder 1)
      - Accounting, 1920 October 20, November 24 (Folder 2)
    - New York - London
      - Incoming (London to New York)
        - General, 1918-1922 (Folder 3)
        - Accounting
          - 1915 May-July (Folder 4)
          - 1916 January-December (Folder 5)
          - 1917 January-November (Folder 6)
          - 1918 January-December (Folder 7)
          - 1919 January-December (Folder 8)
          - 1920 January-December (Folder 9)
          - 1921-1922 (Folder 10)
        - Commercial exchanges, 1919 March-September (Folder 11)
        - Executives (nos. 124-210 with some missing), 1920-1921 (Folder 12)
      - Outgoing (New York to London) (Box 159)
        - Accounting
          - 1915
            - January-June (Folder 1)
            - June-October (Folder 2)
            - October-December (Folder 3)
          - 1916
            - January-March (Folder 4)
            - March-June (Folder 5)
            - June-August (Folder 6)
            - August-September (Folder 7)
            - November-December (Folder 8)
          - 1917
            - January-March (Folder 9)
            - March-June (Folder 10)
            - June-September (Folder 11)
            - September-November (Folder 12)
            - November-December (Folder 13)
            - December (Folder 14)
          - 1918 (Box 160)
            - January-March (Folder 1)
            - March-May (Folder 2)
            - May-August (Folder 3)
            - August-September (Folder 4)
            - September-December (Folder 5)
          - 1919 January-December (Folder 6)
          - 1920 January-December (Folder 7)
          - 1921-1922 (Folder 8)
        - Commercial exchanges (Box 161)
          - 1916 October-December (Folder 1)
          - 1917 January-December (Folder 2)
          - 1918 January-December (Folder 3)
          - 1919 January-March (Folder 4)
    - New York - Rotterdam (Rotterdam to New York) (Folder 5)
      - Accounting, 1916-1918 (Folder 6)
      - Executives (no. 96), 1919 January
    - Washington - London
      - Accounting, 1918 November-December (Folder 7)
      - Commercial exchanges (nos. 2/282-22/302 with some missing), 1919 January-February (Folder 8)
    - Miscellany accounting offices (Folder 9)
  - Financial statements ("journal entries"). Includes accounts, balance sheets, bills, correspondence, invoices, notes, payments, receipts and disbursements, shipping records, etc. (Box 162)
    - 1917 November-December (Folder 1-2)
    - 1918
      - January-July (Folder 3-9)
      - August-October (Folder 10-12)
      - October (Box 163, Folder 1-5)
      - November-December (Box 164, Folder 1-2)
    - 1919
      - January-July (Folder 3-9)
      - August-December (Box 165, Folder 1-5)
    - 1920 January-September (Folder 6-14)
  - Receipts of monetary donations, 1918-1919 (Box 166, Folder 1-5)
  - Remittances of Belgian and French governments. Includes other figures relating to the Belgian Relief Food Program (Folder 6)
  - Voucher register index (accounts #105-107) (Box 167, Folder 1-3)
- NEW YORK OFFICE ALLIED BAZAAR FILE, 1916-1917
  - Bulletin of awards, 1916 June-July (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Circulars. Includes some draft letters, list of names, and miscellaneous printed matter (Folder 2)
  - Correspondence. Includes notes, cross references, brochures, interoffice memoranda, receipts of donation, telegrams, and cables, 1916-1917
    - General (Folder 3)
    - A-CO (Folder 4-7)
    - CO-F (Box 169, Folder 1-4)
    - G-K (Box 170, Folder 1-5)
    - L-P (Box 171, Folder 1-6)
    - Q-V (Box 172, Folder 1-7)
    - W-Z (Box 173, Folder 1-2)
  - Floor plan of the Grand Central Palace, 1916 June 3-14 (Folder 3)
  - Form letters (Folder 4)
  - Letterheads of the Allied Bazaar (Folder 5)
  - Lists
    - Articles hard to sell (Folder 6)
    - Awards
      - Articles awarded but not found (Folder 7)
      - Manhattan Storage & Warehouse Co., 1916 August 15, 18
        - Articles and pictures received from (Folder 8)
        - Items in storage and awarded articles (Folder 9)
        - Untagged articles received from (Folder 10)
    - Donors (Folder 11)
    - Participating and cooperating societies, organizations, and booths (Folder 12)
    - Unsold pictures (Folder 13)
  - Mailing lists
    - General (Folder 14)
    - Prospective participants (Folder 15)
    - Reception Committee (Folder 16)
  - Notifications of award. Includes returned mail (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Payment of services and other miscellaneous expenses (Folder 2)
  - Payroll records, 1916 (Folder 3)
  - Program of events of the Allied Bazaar at the Grand Central Palace, New York City, 1916 June 3-14 (Folder 4)
  - Statement of earnings from the bazaar (Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 6)
- NEW YORK OFFICE BELGIAN KIDDIES FILE, 1916-1917
  - Bank statements - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1916-1918. Includes some receipts and a bank book, 1916 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Letters of acknowledgment for donations
    - Belgian Kiddies, Ltd. (Folder 2)
    - Individual donors. Includes some cables, notes, and miscellaneous interoffice memoranda (Folder 3-23)
  - Lists of contributors and delinquents (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Master forms (blank form letters, cables, and sample certificates of the Belgian Kiddies, Ltd.) (Folder 2)
  - Notices to contributors of overdue monthly payments (Folder 3)
  - Shares sold to mining engineers. Includes some correspondence, notes, etc.
    - #1-100 (Folder 4)
    - #101-200 (Folder 5)
    - #201-300 (Folder 6)
    - #301-400 (Folder 7)
    - #401-500 (Folder 8)
    - #501-600 (Folder 9)
    - #601-700 (Folder 10)
    - #701-800 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - #801-900 (Folder 2)
    - #901-1000 (Folder 3)
    - #1001-1101 (Folder 4)
    - #1102-1200 (Folder 5)
    - #1201-1300 (Folder 6)
    - #1301-1400 (Folder 7)
    - #1401-1500 (Folder 8)
    - #1501-1600 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - #1601-1800 (Folder 2)
    - #1801-1900 (Folder 3)
    - #1901-2000 (Folder 4)
    - #2001-2104 (Folder 5)
    - #2105-2200 (Folder 6)
    - #2201-2330 (Folder 7)
  - Unclaimed certificates and returned mail (Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 9)
- NEW YORK OFFICE BELGIAN TAG DAY FILE, 1916-1917
  - Circulars of the Belgian "Flag Day" in support of the C.R.B. (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Copies of cables and telegrams (Folder 2)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - General. Includes some correspondence to D.A.R., cables, telegrams and legal documents concerning the proper use of the United States emblem in collecting relief for Belgium (Folder 3)
      - A-K (Folder 4-13)
      - L-Z (Box 180, Folder 1-11)
    - Letters
      - Between state officials and D.A.R. officials (Folder 12)
      - For special donations. Includes campaign letters for D.A.R. (Folder 13)
      - From governors, mayors and organizations (Folder 14)
  - Data of total number of chapters in each state and total membership in each state (Folder 15)
  - File of Daisy Allen Story, President General of the National Society of the Daughters of the American Revolution (Folder 16)
  - Instructions for bookkeeping (Folder 17)
  - Lists
    - Individuals who received extra flags (Folder 18)
    - Local chapters that received extra flags (Folder 19)
    - Names of prospective contributors (Folder 20)
    - State chapters of the D.A.R. (Folder 21)
    - State officials receiving telegram on March 18. Also includes names of state regent (Folder 22)
    - Treasurers of state committees (Folder 23)
  - Official pledge and receipt forms for individual and agency donation (Folder 24)
  - Press releases (Folder 25)
  - Proclamations and some correspondence from state governors, officials, and mayors (Folder 26)
  - Receipts (Box 181-194)
- NEW YORK OFFICE CABLES AND TELEGRAMS, 1914-1921
  - General (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - 1914
    - November (Folder 2)
    - December (Folder 3-4)
  - 1915 (Box 196)
    - January (Folder 1-2)
    - February (Folder 3-4)
    - March-July (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - August-December (Folder 2)
  - 1916, New York-London
    - Incoming (London to New York)
      - January (Folder 3)
      - March-May (Folder 4)
      - June-August (Folder 5)
      - September-December (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Outgoing (New York to various offices)
      - February (Folder 2)
      - May (Folder 3)
      - August (Folder 4)
  - 1917 (Box 199)
    - New York-London
      - Incoming (London to New York)
        - January-February (Folder 1)
        - March-April (Folder 2)
        - May-August (Folder 3)
        - September-December (Folder 4)
      - Outgoing (New York to London), December (Folder 5)
    - Washington-London - Outgoing (Washington to London), October-November (Folder 6)
  - 1918 (Box 200)
    - General - Confirmation of copies (Washington, D.C.), November-December (Folder 1)
    - New York-London
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Incoming (London to New York)
        - January-May (Folder 3)
        - June-December (Folder 4)
      - Outgoing (New York to London) (Box 201)
        - January-June (Folder 1)
        - July-December (Folder 2)
    - New York-Washington, D.C., (London to Washington, D.C. via New York office), February-November (Folder 3)
    - Washington, D.C.-London, (London to Washington, D.C.), January-November (Folder 4)
  - 1919
    - General - Confirmation of copies (Washington, D.C.) (Folder 5)
    - New York-Brussels - Incoming (Brussels to New York), April December (Folder 6)
    - New York-London (Folder 7)
      - Incoming (London to New York), March December
      - Outgoing (New York to London), January-November (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - 1920
    - General - Incoming (various offices to New York) (Folder 2)
    - New York-Brussels
      - Incoming (Brussels to New York), February-July (Folder 3)
      - Outgoing (New York to Brussels), March-December (Folder 4)
  - 1921
    - New York - Paris
      - Incoming (Paris to New York) (Folder 5)
      - Outgoing (New York to Paris) (Folder 6)
- NEW YORK OFFICE CORRESPONDENCE, 1914-1919
  - General (Box 203)
    - General
      - General. Includes correspondence with various service companies such as telephone and printing companies for bidding of their services and some notes and clippings (Folder 1-2)
      - Accounting. Letters regarding bank deposits, statement of accounts, and payments (Folder 3)
      - Advertising. Letters from various advertising agencies and departments of major newspaper agencies, magazines, alumni bulletins from universities and colleges. Also contains some clippings, notes, and other materials (Folder 4)
      - Transportation and shipping. Letters concerning shipping and cargo schedules, costs, and payments
        - New York - Antwerp (New York to Antwerp), 1919 (Folder 5)
        - New York - London (New York to London), 1919, January-December (Folder 6)
        - New York - Rotterdam (New York to Rotterdam), 1915-1918 (Folder 7)
    - Alphabetical files
      - A-B (Folder 8-9)
      - C-K (Box 204, Folder 1-9)
      - L-S (Box 205, Folder 1-8)
      - T-Z (Box 206, Folder 1-5)
    - Chronological files, 1914-1915. Outgoing letters, cables, and telegrams (Box 207)
      - 1914
        - November 15-30 (Folder 1-16)
        - December
          - 1-4 (Folder 17-20)
          - 5-15 (Box 208, Folder 1-11)
          - 16-28 (Box 209, Folder 1-13)
          - 29-31 (Box 210, Folder 1-3)
      - 1915
        - January
          - 1-8 (Folder 4-11)
          - 9-19 (Box 211, Folder 1-11)
          - 20-31 (Box 212, Folder 1-12)
        - February (Box 213)
          - 1-9 (Folder 1-9)
          - 10-18 (Box 214, Folder 1-9)
          - 19-28 (Box 215, Folder 1-10)
        - March
          - 1-2 (Folder 11-12)
          - 3-12 (Box 216, Folder 1-10)
          - 13-31 (missing 28th) (Box 217, Folder 1-18)
        - April 21 (Folder 19)
        - June
          - 2 (Folder 20)
          - 7-10 (Folder 21-24)
      - 1916 February 28 (Folder 25)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 26)
  - C.R.B committees, divisions, and miscellany entities, 1916-1920 (Box 218)
    - General
      - General. Includes some telegrams (Folder 1)
      - Incoming
        - Antwerp, 1919 (Folder 2)
        - Brussels, 1916-1918 (Folder 3)
        - London, 1919 (Folder 4)
        - Paris, 1919 (Folder 5)
      - Outgoing
        - Brussels, 1916-1918 (Folder 6)
        - Buenos Ayres, 1917 (Folder 7)
        - London, 1919-1920 (Folder 8)
        - Paris, 1916-1918 (Folder 9)
    - Belgian Lace Cooperative (re: Thomas E. Dawber) (Folder 10)
    - Benevolent Fund Committee (Folder 11)
    - Branch offices and state committees
      - Little Rock, AR (Folder 12)
      - Los Angeles, CA (Folder 13)
      - Denver, CO (Folder 14)
      - Seattle, WA (Folder 15)
    - Clothing Campaign
      - General. Incluces some interoffice memoranda, payrolls, and shipment schedules (Folder 16)
      - Daily reports, 1919
        - Boston, MA (Folder 17)
        - Newark, NJ (Folder 18)
    - Clothing Division
      - General. Includes requisition and shipment records (Folder 19)
      - Boston Office (Folder 20)
      - London Office
        - Incoming (Folder 21)
        - Outgoing (Folder 22)
      - New York Office (Box 219, Folder 1)
      - Newark Office
        - General. Includes some newspaper issues (Folder 2)
        - Kellogg, Douglas (Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous (Folder 4)
    - Commercial Exchanges - London Office - Outgoing (Folder 5)
    - Executive Committees. Includes New York State Executive Committee and minutes of meeting (Folder 6)
    - Executive Department
      - Incoming (Rotterdam to New York), 1915-1918 (Folder 7)
      - Outgoing (New York to Rotterdam), 1915-1918 (Folder 8)
    - Joint Distribution Committee (Folder 9)
    - Lace Department - London Office - Outgoing (Folder 10)
    - Purchasing Department, Shoe Department, and Textile - Outgoing (New York to Rotterdam), 1916-1918 (Folder 11)
  - Countries, 1914-1918. Includes some clippings, telegrams, notes, and other miscellaneous materials (Box 220)
    - Argentina (Folder 1)
    - Belgium (Folder 2)
    - Brazil (Folder 3)
    - Canada
      - Cities
        - Carleton Place (Ont.) (Folder 4)
        - Montreal (Quebec) (Folder 5)
        - Toronto (Ont.) (Folder 6)
      - Provinces
        - Alberta (Folder 7)
        - British Columbia (Folder 8)
        - Manitoba (Folder 9)
        - Nova Scotia (Folder 10)
        - Ottawa (Folder 11)
        - Quebec (Folder 12)
        - Saskatchewan (Folder 13)
    - Chile (Folder 14)
    - China (Folder 15)
    - Cuba (Folder 16)
    - Denmark (Folder 17)
    - France (Folder 18)
    - Germany (Folder 19)
    - Great Britain (Folder 20)
    - Guatemala (Folder 21)
    - Italy (Folder 22)
    - Japan (Folder 23)
    - Mexico (Folder 24)
    - Netherlands (Folder 25)
    - Nicaragua (Folder 26)
    - Norway (Folder 27)
    - Panama (Folder 28)
    - Peru (Folder 29)
    - Philippines (Folder 30)
    - Puerto Rico (Folder 31)
    - South Africa (Folder 32)
    - Switzerland (Folder 33)
    - United States
      - Alabama (Folder 34)
      - California (Folder 35)
      - Colorado (Folder 36)
      - Connecticut (Box 221, Folder 1)
      - Delaware (Folder 2)
      - District of Columbia (Folder 3)
      - Floria (Folder 4)
      - Georgia (Folder 5)
      - Idaho (Folder 6)
      - Illinois (Folder 7)
      - Indiana (Folder 8)
      - Iowa (Folder 9)
      - Kansas (Folder 10)
      - Kentucky (Folder 11)
      - Louisiana (Folder 12)
      - Maine (commodity donations) (Folder 13)
      - Maryland (Folder 14)
      - Massachusetts (Folder 15)
      - Michigan (Box 222, Folder 1)
      - Minnesota (Folder 2)
      - Mississippi (Folder 3)
      - Missouri (Folder 4)
      - Montana (Folder 5)
      - Nebraska (Folder 6)
      - New Hampshire (Folder 7)
      - New Jersey (Folder 8)
      - New Mexico (Folder 9)
      - New York (Folder 10-11)
      - New York (Box 223, Folder 1-2)
      - North Carolina (Folder 3)
      - North Dakota (Folder 4)
      - Ohio (Folder 5)
      - Oklahoma (Folder 6)
      - Oregon (Folder 7)
      - Pennsylvania (Folder 8)
      - Rhode Island (Folder 9)
      - South Carolina (Box 224, Folder 1)
      - South Dakota (Folder 2)
      - Tennessee (Folder 3)
      - Texas (Folder 4)
      - Utah (Folder 5)
      - Vermont (Folder 6)
      - Virginia (Folder 7)
      - Washington (Folder 8)
      - West Virginia (Folder 9)
      - Wisconsin (Folder 10)
      - Wyoming (Folder 11)
    - Venezuela (Folder 12)
  - Individuals, 1917-1919. Includes some memoranda, telegrams, and clippings
    - Allen, Ben S., 1919 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Archer, Mary, 1918-1919 (Folder 2)
    - Arrowsmith, Robert, 1918-1919 (Folder 3)
    - Barrez, G. Joseph, 1918-1919 (Folder 4)
    - Burke, Thomas, 1918-1919 (Folder 5)
    - Carle, Robert W., 1917 (Folder 6)
    - Denegre, George, 1919 (re: Aloysius Laigneil) (Folder 7)
    - Finch, Edgar V., 1917 (Folder 8)
    - Gade, John A., 1919 (Folder 9)
    - Goor, Maurice, 1915-1918 (Folder 10)
    - Henry, Bayard Mrs., 1918-1919 (Folder 11)
    - Hoover, Herbert, 1919 (Folder 12)
    - Hoover, Lou Henry, 1919 (Folder 13)
    - Ide, George E., 1917 (Folder 14)
    - Kassman, Samuel B., 1919 (Folder 15)
    - Kellogg, Vernon, 1919 (Folder 16)
    - Lawrence, George W., 1919 (re: purchases of coffee) (Folder 17)
    - Mapes, Lester D., 1919 (Folder 18)
    - Paderewski, Ignan, 1915-1916 (Folder 19)
    - Wardwell, Allen, 1917 (Folder 20)
    - Wardwell, Florence, 1917 (Folder 21)
    - Whitmarsh, Theodore F. Includes some personal papers (Folder 22)
  - Organizations and groups, 1917-1919 (Box 226)
    - American National Red Cross
      - 1918 (Folder 1)
      - 1919 (Folder 2)
    - American Railway Express Company (Folder 3)
    - American Security and Trust Company (Folder 4)
    - American Yugo-Slav Relief Committee (Folder 5)
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company (Folder 6)
    - Belgian Military Mission, U.S.A. (Folder 7)
    - Belgian Relief Fund (Ontario Branch, Canada) (Folder 8)
    - Boston and Maine Railroad (Folder 9)
    - British Ministry of Food in U.S.A. (Folder 10)
    - California Committee for Relief in Belgium and (Folder 11)
    - California Committee for Relief of Serbia and Northern France (Folder 12)
    - Canadian Mining Institute (Folder 13)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey (Folder 14)
    - Comite de Guatemala de Socorros a Belgica (Folder 15)
    - Comite Franco-Americain Pour La Protection Des Enfants De La Frontiere (Folder 16)
    - Committee for Christian Relief in France and Belgium (Folder 17)
    - Dollar Christmas Fund for Destitute Belgian Children (Folder 18)
    - France. High Commissioner in the United States (Folder 19)
    - Guaranty Trust Company of New York (re: Alexander J. Hemphill) (Folder 20)
    - Johnson and Higgine Average Adjusters and Insurance Brokers (Folder 21)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad Company (Folder 22)
    - McFadden and Brother (Folder 23)
    - National Committee for Relief in Belgium (London, Great Britain) (Folder 24)
    - National Investigation Bureau (Folder 25)
    - National Surety Company (Folder 26)
    - Netherlands. Consulate General (New York City) (Folder 27)
    - New England Belgian Relief Fund (Folder 28)
    - P. N. Gray and Company, Inc. (Folder 29)
    - Relief Work for the Victims of the War in Belgium (Box 227)
      - Montreal (Quebec) (Folder 1)
      - Winnipeg (Folder 2)
    - Textile Alliances, Inc. (Folder 3)
    - United States. Department of Commerce (Folder 4)
    - United States. Department of State (Folder 5)
    - United States. Food Administration. Includes letters of recommendation for employment with the C.R.B. and some interoffice memoranda (Folder 6)
    - United States. Navy Department (Folder 7)